(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T21:12:29.700656",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
[Title: 2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales]
[Title: The concert will be starting soon.]
[Title: Attention For Visitors]
Greetings CC, my fated rival.
Greetings Ina, my destined rival!
And hello to everyone watching from...
Serendipity!
Remember, if you want a chance for your wish to be featured on the Otomo or the Takodachi that we made,
post about it with #WishUponTakoTomo!
Thank you AmiAmi for supporting our rivalry,
and for supporting Serendipity!
Be sure to check out the booth at Anime Expo!
Yeah!
Hey, Pebbles!
It's Koseki Bijou!
And all of hololive BASE is here with me, all 14 of us!
hololive BASE is coming to Round1 USA locations nationwide, starting this September!
Come hang out with us!
Follow @round1usa on Instagram and X so you don't miss out on any updates!
We can't wait to see you there! Bye-bye!
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
The concert will be starting soon. / 開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon. / Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon.
Sing out boldly again
Continuing this odyssey
We'll start this new refrain
Brimming with memories
And when the clouded skies become bright
Let's reunite!
What's up, everyone? Welcome to hololive EN Serendipity!
Yeah! LA, we're back!
Let's kick off the show with Myth Medley!
Ready? 1, 2, 3!
Showtime, baby! I would say, "Today's forecast calls for light delay"
"Heavy wrapping-up-this-stuff, is it really enough?" "Still gotta keep on brewing endlessly," why?
Take it easy! What've we learned? Set a fire in our hearts and the PC burns, ah!
Optimistic, focus on a quick fix! Teach new dogs all of our old tricks!
Circle's stronger than ever and never saying die
And now I'm aware it's so ironic, the world's a freaking lie!
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to empire!
Now losing to you young people in our hearts...
...admit that it's priceless, you know!
Spanning new dimensions
We can bring another mystery to light
Blending our ascension, dancing in time
We ignite
Join us while we're celebrating
In the myth that we're creating
There's another story waiting
Through this world and beyond
Our distant dreams have brought us here
A strong, unyielding bond
Guiding us endlessly
Will bring us moments that we hold dear
Time rushes on
And conflicting winds may scatter us
We'll keep this promise
When the moment's finally right
1, 2, 3!
Realize!
Lights up, floodlights, let's begin
We'll start stage-right and shuffle on in
Get your costumes ready, feel the show
We're jumping for joy, let's go!
Watching the clock so cue the band
We'll keep on entertaining hand in hand
It's our greatest moment yet
A spectacle they'll never forget
Throw a party from dusk till dawn
The show will go on and on
Tell them that we're here to stay
And spread the news from Tokyo to Broadway!
Gleaming, spotlight! Get together, boogieing all night!
Beaming so bright! Now we're feeling alright!
Since the day we met, we've been going strong
And we'll keep moving right along
So keep on dancing! Yeah, you bet!
Nothing can stop us, we're a perfect quintet!
And homies, no matter where we go
It was meant to be, don't you know?
We're gonna feel so alive when it's time to spring
Ready to put on another show!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muse gives whisper, truth or dare
The howls of full blood took the world
But no one's keeping score
Steadfast and tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, well I'm all in
I'll play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in gold and string
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
A liar's chase, a shrouded face
I got to try my luck, keep on spinning fate
Ah, la-ta-ta-ta-tan
I'm always spinning red
Woah, yeah
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flax and string
Casting locks together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
I'll spin back round with every chance I get
The wheel turns in a dire cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
Is this black or red?
I'm moving up ahead
A bogus chance, a daring dance
I've gotta frame my fate with my own hands
La, la, la...
I'm taking fate into my hands
Woah, yeah
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
Blazing fire
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
Tension rising to the top, won't look back, I'll never stop
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot, it's your fault, baby
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
Come on and come on I wanna confess
Baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter
Gonna be wanna be ready for more
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame, keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name, sweet love burn me away
Blazing fire
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm baring my soul
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play a dangerous game
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash
Breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy
Tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough
Fanning the flame of love
And now it's taking over
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame,
Keep me burning,
Fire lover, call my name,
Sweet love, burn me away.
Blazin' fire!
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion,
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream,
Wild desire, fueling my delusion,
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame,
Keep me burning,
Fire lover, call my name,
Sweet love, burn me away.
Blazin' fire!
Gigi Murin
Cecilia Immergreen
AutoFister
CCGG madness,
Otomos now listen,
Grems get in position,
CCGG madness,
Orange green division,
Ooooooh,
Auto Fister,
Hey hey CCGG mad fun,
Hey hey gremlin automaton,
Guten Tag!
Can you tell me where the bathroom is?
I've been walking around all day and I really need to go...
Uh, no,
But I've seen this new super cute cafe around the corner,
And they sell tea and baumkuchen!
Sorry, I don't speak German.
Oh...
On this day you are cursed to cope,
And keep it in your memory,
Oh come on, you're supposed to hope,
And let our brand of madness run its course,
Take our hand, let's fly away,
Break a leg now, challenge fate,
Quick, before your time's up,
Give in and be our playmate,
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await,
Love yourself, don't be afraid,
Sign just one condition,
Give in, release all inhibition,
CCGG CCGG CCGG madness,
Oh CCGG CCGG Auto Fister,
Oh CCGG CCGG, come let's play!
Come on, LA! We wanna hear you shout!
Say something, Gigi!
Oh my god, why won't you say something?!
I don't know what to say, you're looking at me weird!
Oh come on, can a girl not hope
To lose your heart in reverie?
There's no way to divert this trope,
So let our brand of madness run its course,
Take our hand, let's fly away,
Make a way now, choose a date,
Quick, before your time's up,
Give in and be our playmate,
Hop, step, jump, our dreams await,
Love yourself, don't be afraid,
Live up your ambition,
Come on, let go of intuition,
CCGG CCGG CCGG madness,
Oh CCGG CCGG Auto Fister,
Oh CCGG CCGG, come and play!
We are here in LA right now!
Do you wanna join us?
Yeah! Can you even resist right now?
No way! It's an infinity infinity war, hi!
Everyone, are you ready?
Go, go, go!
Are you ready?
Let's go!
All our fun must come to an end,
But at least you've found a friend,
So let us play and stay forever,
Or rather...
Now, together!
Take a hand and let's fly away
Turn around and let us play
Find just one condition, come on
Join in our secret mansion fly
Fly away...
Take my hand, take my hand... Hold my hand...
La, la, la-la-la, la, la, la-la-la...
La, la, come let's play!
Hello, LA!
Hello!
Home to... not-very-far and Shaq's greatest tweets!
My butt's too big for this seat! Ah!
Wow, look at it! It's so big and juicy! How impressive!
Hello, everyone!
It's me, Cecilia Immergreen!
And me, Gigi Murin!
And together, we are...
AUTO...
BESTIES!
Well, LA, we wanted to do...
...some LA call-and-response!
So I'm gonna say something and then you cheer if you like it, okay?
Okay?
The beach!
hololive in LA!
Sitting in traffic!
Whatever.
CCGG in LA!
Yeah!
Okay, we're very excited to be here at hololive...
...So-rad-skibidi! So-rad-skibidi!
Please all stand. It is 4th of July weekend for the flag.
Please stand up, everyone!
Oh say, can you see, by the dawn's early light, what so proud...
Okay, okay, shut up, shut up! That's enough, enough...
Enough of that shit, okay.
How about...
...we do a CCGG chant?
How does it go?
No, no, no! Not yet, not yet!
USAじゃない！ No, no, no!
Not USA! No, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no!
Okay, guys, since you are standing...
...we want you to do our chant of our chorus...
...plus...
...stomping!
To the beat, okay?
So, the left side, we want them to be green!
And this side, green! Orange!
Green! Orange! Do it now!
Quickly.
Okay, perfect, perfect, perfect!
Good.
Okay, okay, okay, stomping...
And then we say CCGG, CCGG.
Yes.
CC-GG!
CC-GG Madness!
CC-GG...
...Auto-Bester!
CC-GG!
CC-GG Madness!
Come, let's play!
一緒に, together!
Together, together!
Everyone together really fast now!
So impress us, okay?
Are you ready? Are you ready?
CC-GG, CC-GG, CC-GG, CC-GG...
...Madness!
CC-GG, CC-GG...
...Auto-Bester!
CC-GG, CC-GG, CC-GG, CC-GG...
...Madness!
CC-GG, CC-GG...
...Come, let's play!
Really impressive, guys!
That was really, really good!
Maybe America IS awesome!
USA! USA! USA!
Yeah, they freaking love us again!
In America!
In America! Well...
...for those at home...
...this is sadly the end of the free section.
So please...
There's one more song, actually! The song after this!
Oh, one more song! Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
Um, but the tickets for the streaming ticket down below...
In the description! Check out the streaming tickets, okay?
I always forget to do this today. Okay?
And...
無料配信は次の曲で最後になります。
The free stream will end after the next song.
ライブの続きはぜひ配信チケットを買ってみてね！
Be sure to buy a stream ticket to watch the rest of the live concert!
買ってみてね！
Please buy it!
Or you're haters! All you freaking haters! Okay?
Don't be a freaking loser, don't hate us.
For the very last part...
...since this is the very first MC, we want you to be...
...as loud as possible, okay?
So...
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Thank you!
We will become...
...a bowling ball and a bowling pin,
and we need you to chant...
"Serendipity", right? Okay?
Keep chanting until we're gone!
Don't stop until we're gone!
Well, one time together, everyone!
Serendipity!
I'll be your exit route
Pound the gavel and sentence me to doom
Even though I'm just doing what you do
Decide which lies become the truth
No, you never really thought about it that far
Judging me when I can see you've got the same scars
That's the price that I pay, it's a deep mark
Come, pick your sacrifice
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected and not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
One request, it's:
Hypocrisy
I've seen what you do in private rings
All your friends, yeah, they know what you really think
To your glory, the masses keep on singing
Point at me in a hurry
Pick a scapegoat for the new controversy
Even when I'm buried, hidden, silent, you'll be wary
Please, dear God, show them mercy
Nail me to your crucifix
Nothing else can fix this
So I'll take the blame
See yourself reflected and not corrected
One request, it's:
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
Break me now
Take me down
Me down
One request, it's:
I see your sins
And they're in your soul
Consume and ignore
Decay to your core
I'll never win to you
But within you'll...
Break, break, break, break
And when I...
You will...
And in your hands, the hammer pounds the nail in
Don't be gentle
Don't be kind when you
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
Poke their eyes out
Leave them blind
Murder, murder, murder the martyr
One request, it's:
Do you love me? Again, again, again
The stars aligned like it was always meant to be
So come along and join me, embracing serendipity
One shooting star, one blaze of light (One time in a lifetime)
One million wishes in the night
Somehow, my dearest dream came true (One time in a lifetime)
I saw this brilliant sky with you
So many roads, so many journeys
But luck decided that today we'd meet
It's serendipity
Ah
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (That's right)
One time in a lifetime
One magic moment that we share (One time in a lifetime)
While music lingers in the air
A song of everlasting bonds (One time in a lifetime)
To warm my heart as time goes on
Each day will bring another journey
With new encounters that are meant to be
It's serendipity
Ah
Miraculous, that we're together in this life
A perfect dance of happenstance that brought us side by side
It's marvelous that though the universe is wide
You're standing here beside me, embracing serendipity
One time in a lifetime (That's right)
One time in a lifetime
This is right where we're meant to be (Sweet, sweet serendipity)
Wishing on stars and chasing after dreams, seeing where they lead
Say it with me, everybody (Serendipity)
Mysterious
Mysterious, a single moment changes fate
The winds and tides that shaped our lives all led us to this day (Oh, ah)
It's wondrous, somehow we met along the way (Ah)
Now here you are beside me, embracing serendipity
We'll shine like shooting stars
In flight tonight
One time in a lifetime (That's right)
One time in a lifetime